<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Story
    title="An Android's Tale"
    author="Nick Rout"
    description="Play the role of Andy the Android as you embark on a quest in the fictional realm of Plex.
Your aim is to acquire each of the twelve sweet treats, scattered far and wide.
Rumours of a mysterious thirteenth treat begin to appear as your story unfolds..."
    image="https://c1.staticflickr.com/5/4031/4637562776_bb88eac229_b.jpg">

    <!-- Image source: https://www.flickr.com/photos/yuyang226/4637562776 -->
    <!-- Labeled for noncommercial reuse -->

    <Achievement name="Cupcake"/>
    <Achievement name="Donut"/>
    <Achievement name="Eclair"/>
    <Achievement name="Froyo"/>
    <Achievement name="Gingerbread"/>
    <Achievement name="Honeycomb"/>
    <Achievement name="Ice Cream Sandwich"/>
    <Achievement name="Jelly Bean"/>
    <Achievement name="KitKat"/>
    <Achievement name="Lollipop"/>
    <Achievement name="Marshmallow"/>
    <Achievement name="Nougat"/>
    <Achievement name="O"/>

    <!-- General requirements: -->
    <!-- Sub-choices should not exceed an amount of 3 (as per App Shortcuts limit of 4 requirement, 1 reserved for 'Show scenario' -->
    <!-- Choice actions should be <= 25 characters in length (due to App Shortcuts limits) -->
    <!-- Provide a valid action_type for each Action, and a valid scenario_type for each Scenario (see below) -->
    <!-- Provide a single Finish and optional Achievement/s at each story ending -->

    <!--
    Action types (determines shortcut color / icon):
        0 - Unknown
        1 - Agree
        2 - Attack
        3 - Buy
        4 - Defend
        5 - Disagree
        6 - Discard
        7 - Drink
        8 - Eat
        9 - Engage
        10 - Exercise
        11 - Fix
        12 - Flee
        13 - Idea
        14 - Inspect
        15 - Keep
        16 - Learn
        17 - Move Left
        18 - Move Right
        19 - Numeric_1
        20 - Numeric_2
        21 - Numeric_3
        22 - Play
        23 - Proceed
        24 - Rest
        25 - Sell
        26 - Stop
        27 - Use
        28 - Wait
    -->

    <!--
    Scenario types (determines notification color / icon / sound / vibrate pattern):
        0 - Unknown
        1 - Achievement
        2 - Challenge
        3 - Conflict
        4 - Direction
        5 - Ending
        6 - Game
        7 - Happy
        8 - Item
        9 - Meal
        10 - Meeting
        11 - Neutral
        12 - Numeric
        13 - Offer
        14 - Preparation
        15 - Problem
        16 - Puzzle
        17 - Requirement
        18 - Transaction
        19 - Unhappy
        20 - Yes No
    -->

    <Choice>
        <Scenario
            scenario_type="15">While immersed in a Daydream, a distant chime catches your attention.
The sound rings again, this time louder and more urgent.
You lift up your headset to see a colorful bicycle whizzing towards you!
        </Scenario>
        <Choice
            action="Move out the way"
            action_type="12">
            <Scenario
                scenario_type="9">The bicycle narrowly misses you and hurtles in to the distance.
It's a bright, busy day in Plex with hundreds of Androids bustling about the common area.
You decide to put your Daydream away and head inside to the cafeteria.
What would you like to eat?
            </Scenario>
            <Choice
                action="Brussel sprouts"
                action_type="8">
                <Scenario
                    scenario_type="20">You pick up a luke-warm green parcel and take a bite.
Brussel sprouts is of one of the two staple foods in Plex.
While you chew on the tasteless, leafy substance, an elderly Android approaches you.
"Are you enjoying that?" he asks.
                </Scenario>
                <Choice
                    action="Yes"
                    action_type="1">
                    <Scenario
                        scenario_type="5">The elderly Android looks disappointed, and bids you farewell.
You continue eating your brussel sprouts, wondering if you have done anything wrong.
                    </Scenario>
                    <Finish/>
                </Choice>
                <Choice
                    action="No"
                    action_type="5">
                    <Scenario
                        scenario_type="2">The elderly Android lights up.
"There was a time when sweet confectioneries and delicious treats were in abundance!" he says.
"Come with me" he whispers, as he hurries out of the cafeteria with surprising speed.
You follow him across the common area, through various alleyways and arrive at a small trapdoor.
You crouch, step through and work your way down a small spiral of stairs into a dimly-lit room.
You find the elderly Android standing in the centre of the room, pointing at six markings etched on the floor.
They include a cylindrical shape, four thin bars and a small, badly-drawn oval.
"These drawings depict half of the sweet treats enjoyed by Androids many clock cycles ago" he says.
"Would you like to taste them for yourself?"
                    </Scenario>
                    <Choice
                        action="No thanks"
                        action_type="5">
                        <Scenario
                            scenario_type="5">You give a hurried goodbye to the elderly Android, head back up the stairs and exit through the trapdoor.
A mixture of confusion and intrigue runs through your CPU as you slowly walk away.
                        </Scenario>
                        <Finish/>
                    </Choice>
                    <Choice
                        action="Sure!"
                        action_type="1">
                        <Scenario
                            scenario_type="8">The elderly Android grins.
"I can offer one of my possessions to assist you on your sugary journey" he says.
You wonder where you will be journeying to and how you will get there, but the excitement of it all overwhelms you.
He holds out his hand, ushering you to choose one of three items.
Which one will you take?
                        </Scenario>
                        <Choice
                            action="Spoon"
                            action_type="19">
                            <Scenario
                                scenario_type="4">You stow the spoon, wondering what it could be used for.
Suddenly, you feel a magnetic pull as the floor seems to sink beneath your feet.
You catch a glimpse of the elderly Android waving goodbye as a blinding light engulfs you.
Before you can say 'Nexus' you land on a grassy patch of land, your image sensors adjusting back to normal light.
"Where am I?" you wonder.
The general topography of the area feels familiar yet different, almost as if you have gone back in time.
You snap out of it and remember that your goal is to locate the sweet treats the elderly Android spoke of.
To your left lies a path that leads into a thick maze of trees.
To your right you notice a young Android dressed in unfamiliar clothes.
What will you do?
                            </Scenario>
                            <Choice
                                action="Walk down path"
                                action_type="17">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="0">You venture down the path, the foliage growing denser with every step.
At one point, you notice the floor crunch beneath your feet.
You find this a bit odd as the ground appears to be soft, due to the layers of leaves and mud.
At one point, the crunching sound is very audible.
You peer down and notice that specks of dark brown and white nestled between the grass.
The specks appears to lead in to a small opening in the trees.
What will you do?
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Proceed on path"
                                    action_type="23">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="19">As you reach the end of the path, a humming sound grows gradually louder.
Something buzzes past your ear.
You have a strong dislike for bugs.
"I'm lost" you mutter, noticing a dead end in front of you.
Your disappointment turns to fear as you look up in horror to see hundreds of winged creatures flying towards you!
You notice a small opening in the trees, a soft golden glow emanating from it.
Act fast!
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Choice
                                        action="Run inside"
                                        action_type="12">
                                        <Scenario
                                            scenario_type="1">You burst through the opening just in time.
Thankfully, your winged opponents do not follow you inside.
While catching your breath, you notice strange hexagonal openings in the walls.
The yellow glow of the room calms your nerves and you decide to inspect them.
Each hexagon appears to hold a thick, golden liquid.
Without thinking, you dip your finger in to one of them and taste it.
It's floral, sticky and sweet.
You have found the Honeycomb treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"Did I imagine that?" you wonder.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                        </Scenario>
                                        <Achieve achievement_name="Honeycomb"/>
                                        <Finish/>
                                    </Choice>
                                </Choice>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Follow them"
                                    action_type="14">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="16">You approach the small opening in the trees.
You lean down, placing your hand next to the opening in order to peer in.
The plants give way and your lose your balance, falling into a small, hollow clearing.
Geometric shapes arranged in a circular pattern are marked on the muddy ground.
Dazed and a little confused, you look up to see a clear glass jar placed on a rock, like a shrine, in the middle of the area.
You cautiously approach it.
What will you do next?
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Choice
                                        action="Open the jar"
                                        action_type="9">
                                        <Scenario
                                            scenario_type="1">A delicious smell escapes the jar and instantly fills the enclosure.
You notice disc-like items in the jar, each dark brown in color with a milky white centre.
You extract one and feel compelled to take a bite.
It's chocolaty, crunchy and sweet.
You have found the mysterious 'O' treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"Was that real?" you wonder.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                        </Scenario>
                                        <Achieve achievement_name="O"/>
                                        <Finish/>
                                    </Choice>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                            <Choice
                                action="Approach Android"
                                action_type="18">
                                <Scenario scenario_type="10">You cautiously approach the young Android.
She turns around, startled but seemingly happy to see you.
"Hello! Who are you?" she says.
"I'm Andy" you reply.
You notice she is holding a small white container, holding a smooth substance that points up from the top.
"I've brought this along to enjoy, but I have nothing to eat it with" she declares.
"I'd offer you some if that weren't the case".
What will you do?
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Use the spoon"
                                    action_type="27">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">You present the spoon and the young Android smiles.
"Here we go, have the first taste" she says, holding up the container.
You take a scoop of the glossy substance place it in your mouth.
It's cold, creamy and sweet.
You have found the Froyo treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"Did that really happen?" you wonder.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Froyo"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                        </Choice>
                        <Choice
                            action="Charging cable"
                            action_type="20">
                            <Scenario
                                scenario_type="3">You put away the charging cable, wondering what it could be used for.
Suddenly, you feel a magnetic pull as the floor seems to sink beneath your feet.
You catch a glimpse of the elderly Android waving goodbye as a blinding light engulfs you.
Before you can say 'Pixel' you land in what appears to be a small village.
"What is this place?" you wonder.
The general topography of the area feels familiar yet different, almost as if you have gone back in time.
You snap out of it and remember that your goal is to locate the sweet treats the elderly Android spoke of.
To your surprise you notice an angry-looking Android, wielding his fists, running towards you!
What will you do?
                            </Scenario>
                            <Choice
                                action="Stand your ground"
                                action_type="4">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="17">The Android slows down as he approaches you, his expression turning from angry to sheepish and his fists lowering.
"Ummm, my job is to defend this village" he stutters.
"I thought you would be afraid."
Although you were startled, you admit to him that he is not very scary.
You strike up a conversation and learn that the village has become quite hostile as a result of the main energy unit having failed.
The inhabitants are without power and it has made them frustrated.
He shows you the energy unit, a large Lithium-ion battery.
You notice that the main cable is bent and frayed towards the base.
Can you fix it?
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Use charging cable"
                                    action_type="11">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">The charging cable is perfect for patching the energy unit.
The battery hums and lights tinkle as the energy flows through the village.
You hear cries of delight all around you and you receive an overwhelming hug from the Android.
"Please, take this, it is the least I can offer for restoring our energy" he says.
He hands you a light-colored item with a cuboid shape, a bit sticky and surprisingly light.
There appear to be items embedded in it
You decide to take a bite.
It's light, chewy, and sweet with an occasional nutty crunch.
You have found the Nougat treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"What was that?" you wonder.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Nougat"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                            <Choice
                                action="Attack!"
                                action_type="2">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="18">You run towards the Android but, to your surprise, he turns around in fear and runs in the opposite direction.
Perplexed, you stand next to a small village hut and decide to inspect your surroundings.
You don't get very far until an elderly female Android emerges from the hut and confronts you.
She ushers you to come inside.
A rich aroma fills your smell sensors.
She points towards a table on which fifty or so small, Android-shaped objects are laid down.
They are flat and a golden-brown color.
She points at them.
"Would you like to buy one?" she asks.
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Yes please"
                                    action_type="3">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">She holds up a NFC pad and you tap your watch on it, transferring some credits.
She hands you one of the objects.
You find the Android shape strange, but the aroma is enticing and you bite in to it.
It's crunchy, fruity, and sweet and melts in your mouth.
You have found the Gingerbread treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"What on Plex..." you wonder.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Gingerbread"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                        </Choice>
                        <Choice
                            action="Rope"
                            action_type="21">
                            <Scenario
                                scenario_type="15">You tie the rope around your waist, wondering what it could be used for.
Suddenly, you feel a magnetic pull as the floor seems to sink beneath your feet.
You catch a glimpse of the elderly Android waving goodbye as a blinding light engulfs you.
Before you can say 'Galaxy' you land with a splash in a rapid river.
"Help!" you yell with all of your speakers' might, but there is no one in sight.
You calm down and remember that your goal is to locate the sweet treats the elderly Android spoke of.
Realising you need to act fast, you notice a patch of reeds between yourself and the river bank.
What will you do?
                            </Scenario>
                            <Choice
                                action="Use the rope"
                                action_type="27">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="11">You untie the rope from your waist and sling it towards the reeds.
Luckily, they latch on and hold tight.
You pull yourself towards the river bank, exhausted and drenched in water.
You take a look back at the reeds and notice they are uniform in shape and texture.
"I must be imagining things" you mutter, but you have a nagging suspicion.
What will you do?
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Take one"
                                    action_type="15">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">You were right!
You quickly notice that it is certainly not a reed.
The outside is brown and glossy, with writing - in a language you don't recognise - engraved in the surface.
The inside is appears dry and almost hollow.
Your exhaustion has lead to hunger and you decide to take a bite.
It's crispy, chocolaty, and sweet.
You have found the KitKat treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"I must be going crazy" you think.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="KitKat"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                            <Choice
                                action="Keep floating"
                                action_type="28">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="6">You have all but given up hope, when you feel yourself being lurched to the side.
A Android has grabbed hold of you and is swimming you to the river bank.
When you reach the side, he laughs and pats you on the back.
"That was a close one!" he exclaims.
"Thank you for saving me" you say, breathing a sigh of relief.
"Is there anything I can do to repay you?"
He scratches his head and appears to quickly make up his mind.
He extracts a pack of cards, with markings on them you've never seen, and holds them out towards you.
"I've been practising my magic but I don't have anyone to test it on, so pick one!" he exclaims.
"Wanna play?"
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Pick a card"
                                    action_type="22">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">You draw a card, being careful not to show him.
He puts it back in to the deck, shuffles, performs some magic and extracts it.
"Is this the one?" he asks.
After inspecting it and seeing that it is your card, you nod, much to his enjoyment.
"You look worn out from your river adventure" he says.
"Here, take this" he says, offering you some kind of a puffy item wrapped in colorful paper.
Figuring it is some kind of food, you take a bite.
It's light, fluffy, and sweet with a sugary layer on top.
You have found the Cupcake treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"I must be going crazy" you think.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Cupcake"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                        </Choice>
                    </Choice>
                </Choice>
            </Choice>
            <Choice
                action="Porridge"
                action_type="8">
                <Scenario
                    scenario_type="20">You take a spoonful.
Porridge is one of the two staple foods in Plex.
While you chew on the tasteless, gooey substance, an elderly Android approaches you.
"Are you enjoying that?" he asks.
                </Scenario>
                <Choice
                    action="Yes"
                    action_type="1">
                    <Scenario
                        scenario_type="5">The elderly Android looks disappointed, and bids you farewell.
You continue eating your porridge, wondering if you have done anything wrong.
                    </Scenario>
                    <Finish/>
                </Choice>
                <Choice
                    action="No"
                    action_type="5">
                    <Scenario
                        scenario_type="2">The elderly Android lights up.
"There was a time when sweet confectioneries and delicious treats were in abundance!" he says.
"Come with me" he whispers, as he hurries out of the cafeteria with surprising speed.
You follow him across the common area, through various alleyways and arrive at a small, run-down building.
You step through the open door.
The room is empty.
You find the elderly Android standing next to a dusty wall, pointing at six markings on its surface.
They include some kind of ring, a hexagonal structure and what appears to be a small figure.
"These drawings depict half of the sweet treats enjoyed by Androids many clock cycles ago" he says.
"Do you want to experience their sugary goodness?"
                    </Scenario>
                    <Choice
                        action="No ways"
                        action_type="5">
                        <Scenario
                            scenario_type="5">You give a hurried goodbye to the elderly Android and exit the small building.
A mixture of confusion and intrigue runs through your CPU as you slowly walk away.
                        </Scenario>
                        <Finish/>
                    </Choice>
                    <Choice
                        action="Definitely!"
                        action_type="1">
                        <Scenario
                            scenario_type="8">The elderly Android grins.
"You may need assistance on your tasty journey." he says.
"I am willing to part with one of my possessions."
You wonder where you will be journeying to and how you will get there, but the excitement of it all overwhelms you.
He holds out his hand, ushering you to choose one of three items.
Which one will you take?
                        </Scenario>
                        <Choice
                            action="LED bulb"
                            action_type="19">
                            <Scenario
                                scenario_type="16">You stash the LED bulb, wondering what it could be used for.
Suddenly, you feel a magnetic pull as the walls seems close in on you.
You catch a glimpse of the elderly Android waving goodbye as a blinding light engulfs you.
Before you can say 'Optimus' you land in a rocky cave with very little light.
"What is this?" you wonder.
You come to your senses and remember that your goal is to locate the sweet treats the elderly Android spoke of.
You see a small, metal device device on the floor and pick it up.
You notice it has two small openings on the top.
What will you do?
                            </Scenario>
                            <Choice
                                action="Insert LED"
                                action_type="13">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="7">To your delight, the device fills the cave with bright light.
You look around you and notice that strangely-shaped stalactites hang from the ceiling.
They're long and thin, with spheres of all different colors on their ends.
They are peculiar but intriguing.
What will you do?
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Break one off"
                                    action_type="9">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">The object is strangely symmetrical, almost as if it had been hand-crafted.
It's not rocky, like your surroundings, but glossy and semi-transparent.
Something compels you to taste it.
It's fruity and sweet.
You have found the Lollipop treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"Interesting..." you think.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Lollipop"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                            <Choice
                                action="Continue"
                                action_type="23">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="20">The cave is dark and you are barely getting anywhere.
On top of that, you are quite hungry.
With no light, you do not have many options.
What will you do?
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Feel around"
                                    action_type="14">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">You place your hand on the floor in the hope of finding something useful.
Alas, you find only cave pebbles.
You hold them in your hand, struggling to come up with any more ideas.
Strangely, the pebbles seem to be softening in your hands.
You lift up your hand and a sweet aroma catches your senses.
"What are these?" you wonder.
Without thinking, you pop one in your mouth.
It's fruity, chewy, and sweet with a sour zing.
You have found the Jelly Bean treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"Strange..." you think.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Jelly Bean"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                        </Choice>
                        <Choice
                            action="A pair of boots"
                            action_type="20">
                            <Scenario
                                scenario_type="2">You put on the boots, wondering if they will come in handy.
Suddenly, you feel a magnetic pull as the walls seems close in on you.
You catch a glimpse of the elderly Android waving goodbye as a blinding light engulfs you.
Before you can say 'Xperia' you land on a snowy slope, a blizzard howling around you.
You let out an audible "Brrr" as your thermometer begins to drop.
You try to ignore the temperature and remember that your goal is to locate the sweet treats the elderly Android spoke of.
Thankfully, your boots prevent you from slipping on the ice and allow you to move around.
The slope looks like a challenging climb, but it's not impossible.
What will you do?
                            </Scenario>
                            <Choice
                                action="Climb"
                                action_type="10">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="17">The boots come in handy as you traverse up the slope.
It seems like an eternity but you manage to reach a plateau where you notice a large cube of ice and a pick axe lying next to it.
Inside the cube, you spot a vague outline of an item, brown and white in color.
"What is that?" you wonder.
What will you do?
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Dig!"
                                    action_type="9">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">You pick up the axe and begin to chip away at the surface.
It takes a long time but you are compelled to get to the item at the centre.
You reach it and it falls from the cube, on to the snow.
You pick it up and notice a frozen white substance nestled between two brown, pitted layers.
You're exhausted and, somehow, the item seems edible.
You sink your teeth in to it, despite how cold it is.
It's cold, creamy, and sweet with a chewy outer layer.
You have found the Ice Cream Sandwich treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"That's odd" you mumble.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Ice Cream Sandwich"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                            <Choice
                                action="Clear the snow"
                                action_type="13">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="8">You decide to clear the immediate snow around you to build a bunker to shelter you.
You dig and dig, almost endlessly, but you eventually form some kind of a shelter.
On your last scoop of snow, your hand hits a wooden surface.
Your energy rejuvenated by intrigue, you keep digging and unearth a small box.
What will you do?
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Open the box"
                                    action_type="9">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">Inside the box you find two cylindrical objects, one a light pink and the other white.
They remind you of clouds and they feel soft to the touch.
All this digging in the cold has made you hungry.
Without thinking, you pop one of the objects in to your mouth.
It's soft, fluffy, and sweet.
You have found the Marshmallow treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"I wonder..." you mumble.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Marshmallow"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                        </Choice>
                        <Choice
                            action="Bottle of water"
                            action_type="21">
                            <Scenario
                                scenario_type="14">You tuck away the button, unsure of its significance.
Suddenly, you feel a magnetic pull as the walls seems close in on you.
You catch a glimpse of the elderly Android waving goodbye as a blinding light engulfs you.
Before you can say 'OnePlus' you land in the centre of a field.
You can barely see past the tops of the beige-colored plants.
You remember that your goal is to locate the sweet treats the elderly Android spoke of, but you are rather fatigued.
What will you do?
                            </Scenario>
                            <Choice
                                action="Rest"
                                action_type="24">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="13">You doze off almost instantly and wake up some time after, feeling revitalised.
You notice you are not alone in the field.
A few other Androids dressed in denim are walking around, gathering the dried plants surrounding you.
You wave at one of them and he makes his way towards you.
"Howdy, partner" he exclaims.
After a fair bit of conversation, you determine he comes from a family of 'bakers' (a word you have never heard of).
"How about a sample of our goods?" he asks.
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Sure"
                                    action_type="1">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">He reaches in to his backpack and pulls out a cardboard carton.
He opens it up and you take a look inside.
You see 6 ring-shaped items, each with a glossy shell covering their tops.
"Well, go ahead" he says.
You don't hesitate to grab a pink-colored one and take a mouthful.
It's warm, doughy, and sweet.
You have found the Donut treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"Huh, weird" you think.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Donut"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                            <Choice
                                action="Drink water"
                                action_type="7">
                                <Scenario
                                    scenario_type="10">The water provides you with some much-needed energy.
You notice a thin wisp of smoke in the distance and decide to walk towards it.
You find that the source of the smoke is a small, stone house with a sign on it that reads "The Bakers".
Intrigued by this strange word, you enter the house.
An Android is sitting at a table, engrossed in a task involving a large, white funnel from which she is piping a strange mixture.
"Hi there" she says as she looks up.
"These are fresh out of the oven, would you like to buy one?"
                                </Scenario>
                                <Choice
                                    action="Yeah!"
                                    action_type="3">
                                    <Scenario
                                        scenario_type="1">She hands you an item that appears to be holding the same substance she was piping.
There is a thin, brown shell on the top of it, which cracks as you take it in yiur hand.
It looks enticing, so you bite in to it.
It's creamy, chocolaty, and sweet with a doughy consistency.
You have found the Eclair treat!

As you finish savouring on it, you feel the same magnetic pull that brought you to this place.
With a bright flash of light, you are pulled away and thrown back in to Plex.
Upon arrival, you seem to have only cached a vague memory of your adventure.
"That can't be real" you think.
Unsure of it all, you decide to relax for now and postpone thinking about it until lunch time.
You put on your Daydream headset...
                                    </Scenario>
                                    <Achieve achievement_name="Eclair"/>
                                    <Finish/>
                                </Choice>
                            </Choice>
                        </Choice>
                    </Choice>
                </Choice>
            </Choice>
        </Choice>
        <Choice
            action="Stand still"
            action_type="28">
            <Scenario
                scenario_type="5">The bicycle begins to slow down rapidly as the rider hastily applies the breaks.
It stops just before you and the owner is not impressed.
The Android huffs and rides away.
"That was close" you mutter out loud, wondering how you could have handled the situation better.
You decide to get back to Daydreaming in order to stop thinking about it.
            </Scenario>
            <Finish/>
        </Choice>
    </Choice>

</Story>